John V. Dowdy, Sr. papers, Inclusive: 1926-1986, undated; Bulk: 1952-1972, undated.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1952-1972; 6
  - 89th Congress, 1965-1966; 9
    - Topical, 2
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Information Relating to Local Employment Created by the Accelerated Public Works Program, 1966 February (Box 381, Folder 15)
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Lack of Compliance with Statutory Requirement for Local Financial Participation in Area Redevelopment Project, 1965 July (Box 381, Folder 16)
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Nation’s Business, 1965 (Box 381, Folder 17)
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Need for Increased Efforts to Minimize Rental Delinquencies on Acquired Properties, 1966 January (Box 382, Folder 1)
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Questionable Basis for Approving Loans for the Construction of Three Motels, 1965 October (Box 382, Folder 2)
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Scientific American, 1965 September (Box 382, Folder 3)
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Summary of the Urban Renewal Program, 1966 November (Box 382, Folder 4)
      - Urban Renewal, Request Research Information, 1965 (Box 382, Folder 5)
      - Urban Renewal, State and Local Plans, 1965 (Box 382, Folder 6)
      - Veterans, 1965 (Box 382, Folder 7)
      - Veterans, 1966 (Box 382, Folder 8)
      - Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Box 382, Folder 9)
      - Vietnam, Publications, “Third Face of War”, 1965 (Box 382, Folder 10)
      - Wage and Hour, 1965 (Box 382, Folder 11)
      - Wage and Hour, 1966 (Box 382, Folder 12)
      - Welfare, 1965 (Box 382, Folder 13)
  - 90th Congress, 1967-1968; 10
    - Sponsored Bills, 1
      - HR 509: Communications Act of 1934 Amendment, 1967 (Box 382, Folder 14)
      - HR 847: Select Committee to Investigate East-West Trade Partners Ability to Supply Communist Countries, 1967 (Box 382, Folder 15)
      - HR 2529: Act of September 8, 1960 Amendment — Washington Channel Waterfront, 1967 (Box 382, Folder 16)
      - HR 2530: District of Columbia Charitable Solicitation Act Amendment, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - HR 2661: For the Relief of E. F. Fort, Cora Lee Fort Corbett, and W. R. Fort, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 2)
      - HR 3289: Career Compensation Act of 1949 Amendment, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 3)
      - HR 5137: Compensation to Survivors of Law Enforcement Officers Killed While Apprehending Federal Crime Offender, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 4)
      - HR 5138: Kenilworth National Capital Park in the District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 5)
      - HR 5990: District of Columbia Charitable Solicitation Act Amendment - Mattachine Society, 1967-1968 (Box 383, Folder 6)
      - HR 7831: Amend the Fire and Casualty Act and the Motor Vehicle Safety Responsibility Act of the District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 7)
      - HR 9059: District of Columbia Unemployment Compensation Act Amendment, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 8)
      - HR 10008: Revision of the Quota-Control System on the Importation of Meats, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 9)
      - HR 10180: Regulation of Imports of Milk and Dairy Products, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 10)
      - HR 10783: Crime and Criminal Procedure in the District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 11)
      - HR 10985: For the relief of Dr. Lorenzo Galatas, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 12)
      - HR 11609: Dam B Reservoir on the Neches River, TX, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 13)
      - HR 11816: Benefits for Law Enforcement Officers Not Employed by U.S. who are Killed or Injured while Apprehending Violators of Federal Law, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 14)
      - HR 12506: Authorize Commissioners to Manage and Collect Rent for Occupancy of Space on the Streets of D.C., 1967 (Box 383, Folder 15)
      - HR 12507: Authorize Commissioners to Lease Airspace in D.C., 1967 (Box 383, Folder 16)
      - HR 13480: Amend Section 39(a) of the Motor Vehicle Safety Responsibility Act, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 17)
      - HR 14098: Amend Act to Provide Annual Inspection for Vehicles in the District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 18)
      - HR 14430: To Establish a Commissioner of Police for the District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 19)
      - HR 14566: Protective Eye Devices for Students and Teachers in the District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 20)
      - HR 15131: District of Columbia Police and Fireman’s Salary Act of 1958 Amendment, 1968 (Box 383, Folder 21)
      - HR 15147: Immigration and Nationality Act Amendment to Provide for Naturalization for Armed Forces Combat Personnel, 1968 (Box 383, Folder 22)
      - HR 17502: Authorize the Commissioner of the District of Columbia to Utilize Volunteers for Active Police Duty, 1968 (Box 383, Folder 23)
      - HCR 389: Jurisdiction over the Panama Canal Zone, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 24)
      - HCR 659: To Require France to Pay Its World War I Debt, 1968 (Box 383, Folder 25)
      - HJR 44: Proposed Amendment the Constitution of the United States to Permit Voluntary Participation in Prayer in Public Schools, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 26)
      - HJR 154: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution of the United States Relative to Equal Rights for Men and Women, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 27)
      - HJR 155: Proposed Amendment the Constitution of the United States to Guarantee the Right to Any State to Apportion One House of its Legislature on Factors Other than Population, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 28)
      - HJR 157: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution of the United States for the Election of the President and Vice President, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 29)
      - HJR 1209: Family Reunion Day, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 30)
    - Topical, 2
      - Alaska, 1968 (Box 383, Folder 31)
      - Appropriations, 1967 (Box 383, Folder 32)
      - Automobiles, 1967-1968 (Box 383, Folder 33)
      - Banks and Banking, 1967-1968 (Box 383, Folder 34)
      - Civil Rights, 1967 (Box 384, Folder 1)
      - Civil Rights, Data, 1967 (Box 384, Folder 2)
      - Civil Rights, Guaranteed Income, 1968 (Box 384, Folder 3)
      - Civil Rights, Poor People’s March, 1968 (Box 384, Folder 4)
      - Civil Service, 1967-1968 (Box 384, Folder 5)
      - Communications, General, 1968 (Box 384, Folder 6)
      - Communications, Radio and TV, 1967 (Box 384, Folder 7)
      - Communism, 1967-1968 (Box 384, Folder 8)
      - Conservation, 1967-1968 (Box 384, Folder 9)
      - Constituent Opinions of Multiple Issues, 1976-1968 (Box 384, Folder 10)
      - Credit, Truth in Lending, 1968 (Box 384, Folder 11)
      - Crime, 1967-1968 (Box 384, Folder 12)
      - Daylight Savings Time, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 1)
      - Defense, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 2)
      - Education, General, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 3)
      - Education, General, 1968 (Box 385, Folder 4)
      - Education, Appropriations, 1967-1968 (Box 385, Folder 5)
      - Education, Data, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 6)
      - Electoral College, 1968 (Box 385, Folder 7)
      - Electoral College, Publications, “The Electoral College — Why It Ought to be Abolished”, 1968 (Box 385, Folder 8)
      - Eminent Domain, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 9)
      - Federal Spending, 1968 (Box 385, Folder 10)
      - Finance, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 11)
      - Foreign Aid, 1967-1968 (Box 385, Folder 12)
      - Foreign Trade, 1967-1968 (Box 386, Folder 1)
      - Forestry, 1967-1968 (Box 386, Folder 2)
      - Gold, 1968 (Box 386, Folder 3)
      - Health, 1967-1968 (Box 386, Folder 4)
      - Highways, 1967-1968 (Box 386, Folder 5)
      - Holiday Standardization, 1967 (Box 386, Folder 6)
      - Hospitals, 1967 (Box 386, Folder 7)
      - Housing (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 386, Folder 8)
      - Housing (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 386, Folder 9)
      - Interior, 1967-1968 (Box 386, Folder 10)
      - Interstate Commerce, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 1)
      - Liquor, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 2)
      - Lobbying, 1967 (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - Medical Treatment, 1967 (Box 387, Folder 4)
      - Merchant Marines, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 5)
      - Military, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 6)
      - Military, Appropriations, 1968 (Box 387, Folder 7)
      - Minimum Wage, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 8)
      - Petroleum, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 9)
      - Pollution, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 10)
      - Pollution, Air, 1967 (Box 387, Folder 11)
      - Pollution, Air and Water, 1968 (Box 387, Folder 12)
      - Pollution, Water, Publications, “Federal Water Pollution Control Act”, 1967 (Box 387, Folder 13)
      - Pollution, Water, Publications, Various, 1967-1968 (Box 387, Folder 14)
      - Postal, 1967 (Box 387, Folder 15)
      - Postal, 1968 (Box 387, Folder 16)
      - Poverty Programs, 1967 (Box 387, Folder 17)
      - Publications, “The Budget in Brief: Fiscal Year 1969”, 1968 (Box 387, Folder 18)
      - Publications, “The Crutch that Cripples: Drug Dependence”, 1968 (Box 387, Folder 19)
      - Publications, “National Limestone Institute-Convention Highlights”, 1967 (Box 387, Folder 20)
      - Publications, Politics, vol. 3, no. 2, 1967 January-February (Box 387, Folder 21)
      - Publications, “Proposals to Amend the Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Act”, 1968 (Box 388, Folder 1)
      - Publications, “Proposed Buffalo National River,” Arkansas, 1968 (Box 388, Folder 2)
      - Publications, “The Truth-In-Lending Bill”, 1967 (Box 388, Folder 3)
      - Railroad Retirement, 1967 (Box 388, Folder 4)
      - Railroads, 1967 (Box 388, Folder 5)
      - Rat Control, 1967 (Box 388, Folder 6)
      - Recreation, 1967-1968 (Box 388, Folder 7)
      - Requests, 1967 (Box 388, Folder 8)
      - Resolutions from Various Organizations, 1967-1968 (Box 388, Folder 9)
      - Riots and Rioting, 1967-1968 (Box 388, Folder 10)
      - Selective Service, 1967-1968 (Box 388, Folder 11)
      - Small Business, 1967 (Box 388, Folder 12)
      - Social Security (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 388, Folder 13)
      - Social Security (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 388, Folder 14)
      - Social Security, 1967-1968 (Box 388, Folder 15)
      - Supreme Court, 1967-1968 (Box 389, Folder 1)
      - Surplus Property, 1967-1968 (Box 389, Folder 2)
      - Tariff, 1967-1968 (Box 389, Folder 3)
      - Taxes, General (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 389, Folder 4)
      - Taxes, General (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 389, Folder 5)
      - Taxes, General, 1968 (Box 389, Folder 6)
      - Taxes, Income, 1967 (Box 389, Folder 7)
      - Taxes, Increases (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 389, Folder 8)
      - Taxes, Increases (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 389, Folder 9)
      - Taxes, Increases (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 389, Folder 10)
      - Taxes, Travel, 1968 (Box 390, Folder 1)
      - Textiles, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 2)
      - Trading Stamps, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 3)
      - Transportation, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 4)
      - Treaties, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 5)
      - Truth in Packaging, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 6)
      - Un-American Activities, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 7)
      - United Nations, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 8)
      - Urban Renewal, General, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 9)
      - Urban Renewal, Alabama, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 10)
      - Urban Renewal, California, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 11)
      - Urban Renewal, Connecticut, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 12)
      - Urban Renewal, District of Columbia, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 13)
      - Urban Renewal, Illinois, 1968 (Box 390, Folder 14)
      - Urban Renewal, Indiana, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 15)
      - Urban Renewal, Iowa, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 16)
      - Urban Renewal, Louisiana, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 17)
      - Urban Renewal, Maryland, 1968 (Box 390, Folder 18)
      - Urban Renewal, Massachusetts, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 19)
      - Urban Renewal, Michigan, 1967-1968 (Box 390, Folder 20)
      - Urban Renewal, Mississippi, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 21)
      - Urban Renewal, Montana, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 22)
      - Urban Renewal, Nebraska, 1967 (Box 390, Folder 23)
      - Urban Renewal, New York, 1967 (Box 391, Folder 1)
      - Urban Renewal, Ohio, 1967-1968 (Box 391, Folder 2)
      - Urban Renewal, Pennsylvania, 1967-1968 (Box 391, Folder 3)
      - Urban Renewal, South Dakota, 1967 (Box 391, Folder 4)
      - Urban Renewal, Texas, 1967-1968 (Box 391, Folder 5)
      - Urban Renewal, Washington, 1967 (Box 391, Folder 6)
      - Urban Renewal, Publications, Articles, 1967-1968 (Box 391, Folder 7)
      - Veterans, 1967 (Box 391, Folder 8)
      - Veterans, 1968 (Box 391, Folder 9)
      - Veterans, Data, 1967-1968 (Box 391, Folder 10)
      - Vietnam, 1967 (Box 391, Folder 11)
      - Vietnam, 1968 (Box 391, Folder 12)
      - Vietnam, Publications, “Thoughts on Vietnam”, 1967 (Box 392, Folder 1)
      - Vietnam, Publications, “Vietnam: An Evangelistic War with Catholic Overtones”, 1967 (Box 392, Folder 2)
      - Wage and Hour, 1967-1968 (Box 392, Folder 3)
      - Welfare, 1967-1968 (Box 392, Folder 4)
  - 91st Congress, 1969-1970; 11
    - Sponsored Bills, 1
      - HR 593 and 596: Jurisdiction over the Panama Canal, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 5)
      - HR 636: Support for President in Negotiating Peace in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 6)
      - HR 665: Commends Servicemen and Veterans from the Vietnam Conflict, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 7)
      - HR 700: New Mobilization Committee to End War in Vietnam Investigation Authorization, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 8)
      - HR 926: Select Committee to Investigate Associate Justice of the Supreme Court William Orville Douglas Authorization, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 9)
      - HR 2650: To Designate the Area of Dam B Reservoir on the Neches River, Texas, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 10)
      - HR 2651: Career Compensation Act of 1949 Amendment, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 11)
      - HR 2747: Establish a Commissioner of Police for the District of Columbia, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 12)
      - HR 2856: For the Relief of E. F. Fort, Cora Lee Fort Corbett, and W. R. Fort, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 13)
      - HR 5364: For the Relief of Henry E. Dooley, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 14)
      - HR 9526: District of Columbia Unemployment Compensation Act Amendment, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 15)
      - HR 9527: Authorize the Commissioner of the District of Columbia to Utilize Volunteers for Active Police Duty, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 16)
      - HR 9528: To Require Protective Eye Devices in the District of Columbia Public Schools, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 17)
      - HR 9529: Amend Title 13 of the United States Code Dealing with Census Questions, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 18)
      - HR 9727: Submerged Lands Act Amendment, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 19)
      - HR 9923: Amend Title 18 of the United States Code (Anti-Obscenity), 1969 (Box 392, Folder 20)
      - HR 10335: Revision of Criminal Laws of the District of Columbia Relating to Offenses against Commercial Lodging, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 21)
      - HR 10336: Revision of Laws Relating to the Liability of Commercial Lodging Establishments, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 22)
      - HR 10337: Redesignate Hearing Examiner as Administrative Trial Judge, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 23)
      - HR 13055: Extend Benefits to Officers Killed or Disabled in Line of Duty, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 24)
      - HR 13690: District of Columbia Bail Agency Act Amendment, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 25)
      - HR 14100: Anti-obscenity Legislation, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 26)
      - HR 14224: Amend District of Columbia Code Regarding Juvenile Delinquency Proceedings, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 27)
      - HR 14391: To Establish the Big Thicket National Monument in Texas, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 28)
      - HR 14998: Require Bond to Cover Cost of Holding a Demonstration, Parade, March, or Vigil on Federal Property, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 29)
      - HR 15356: Immigration and Nationality Act Amendment, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 30)
      - HR 15555: Abolish the Commission on Revision of the Criminal Laws of the District of Columbia, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 31)
      - HR 15587: District of Columbia Redevelopment Act of 1945 Amendment (Urban Renewal), 1970 (Box 392, Folder 32)
      - HR 16083: “Nondiscriminatory Education Act” (Attending Neighborhood Schools), 1970 (Box 392, Folder 33)
      - HR 16196: Juvenile Courts in the District of Columbia, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 34)
      - HR 16988: To Increase Salaries of District of Columbia Police, Firemen, and Teachers, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 35)
      - HR 17138: To Increase Salaries of District of Columbia Police, Firemen, and Teachers, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 36)
      - HR 17761: Orderly Trade in Textile and Leather Footwear, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 37)
      - HR 18142: “National Catastrophic Illness Protection Act of 1970” (Box 392, Folder 38)
      - HR 18813: Older Americans Act of 1965 Amendment, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 39)
      - HR 19036: Public Health Service Act Amendment, 1970 (Box 392, Folder 40)
      - HCR 90: Expressing the Sense of the Congress that Aid and Trade with Any Country which Extends Any Aid or Assistance to North Vietnam Shall Be Prohibited, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 41)
      - HCR 420: Revocation of the United Nations Economic Sanctions against Southern Rhodesia, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 42)
      - HCR 436: Protecting Religious Rights of American Astronauts, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 43)
      - HJR 208: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution of the United States Relative to Equal Rights for Men and Women, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 44)
      - HJR 209: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution of the United States for Voluntary Prayer in Public Schools, 1969 (Box 392, Folder 45)
      - HJR 313: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution of the United States for the Election of the President and Vice President (Electoral College), 1969 (Box 392, Folder 46)
      - HJR 791: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution of the United States for the Election of the President and Vice President (Electoral College), 1969 (Box 392, Folder 47)
    - Topical, 2
      - General, 1969-1970 (Box 393, Folder 1)
      - Internal Security, 1970 (Box 391, Folder 2)
      - General, Publications, “Review-1970 Session of Congress”, 1971 (Box 393, Folder 3)
      - Advertising, 1970 (Box 393, Folder 4)
      - Aging, 1970 (Box 393, Folder 5)
      - Agriculture, Publications, Economic Aspects of Farm Program Payment Limitations, 1969 November 6 (Box 393, Folder 6)
      - Agriculture, Publications, Impact: Annual Report 1969 Agricultural Research in Texas, 1970 (Box 393, Folder 7)
      - Animals, 1969 (Box 393, Folder 8)
      - Arms Control, 1970 (Box 393, Folder 9)
      - Automobile Safety, 1969-1970 (Box 393, Folder 10)
      - Banks and Banking, 1969-1970 (Box 393, Folder 11)
      - Big Thicket, 1970 (Box 393, Folder 12)
      - Census, 1969-1970 (Box 393, Folder 13)
      - Civil Rights, 1969-1970 (Box 393, Folder 14)
      - Civil Rights, PRIDE, Inc., 1969 (Box 393, Folder 15)
      - Civil Service, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 1)
      - Communications, Radio and TV, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 2)
      - Communism, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 3)
      - Communism, Publications, “More Deadly Than War-The Communist Revolution in America”, 1969 (Box 394, Folder 4)
      - Conservation, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 5)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 6)
      - Constituent Opinions of Multiple Issues, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 7)
      - Consumer Protection, 1970 (Box 394, Folder 8)
      - Copper Industry, 1970 (Box 394, Folder 9)
      - Copyrights, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 10)
      - Credit, General, 1969-1979 (Box 394, Folder 11)
      - Crime, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 12)
      - Defense, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 13)
      - Drugs, 1969-1970 (Box 394, Folder 14)
      - Education, General, 1969 (Box 394, Folder 15)
      - Education, General, 1970 (Box 394, Folder 16)
      - Education, Appropriations, 1969-1970 (Box 395, Folder 1)
      - Education, Freedom of Choice, Busing, 1970 (Box 395, Folder 2)
      - Electoral College, 1969-1970 (Box 395, Folder 3)
      - Employment, 1970 (Box 395, Folder 4)
      - Environment, 1969-1970 (Box 395, Folder 5)
      - Ethics in Government, 1970 (Box 395, Folder 6)
      - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1970 (Box 395, Folder 7)
      - Finance, 1970 (Box 395, Folder 8)
      - Flags, 1970 (Box 395, Folder 9)
      - Flood Control, 1970 (Box 395, Folder 10)
      - Foreign Aid, 1969-1970 (Box 395, Folder 11)
      - Foreign Relations, 1969-1970 (Box 395, Folder 12)
      - Foreign Relations, Briefing on Rhodesia for Congressional Candidates and Political Leaders, 1969-1970 (Box 395, Folder 13)
      - Foreign Trade, 1969-1970 (Box 395, Folder 14)
      - Forestry, 1969-1970 (Box 396, Folder 1)
      - Health, 1969 (Box 396, Folder 2)
      - Health (1 of 3), 1970 (Box 396, Folder 3)
      - Health (2 of 3), 1970 (Box 396, Folder 4)
      - Health (3 of 3), 1970 (Box 396, Folder 5)
      - Highways (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 396, Folder 6)
      - Highways (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 396, Folder 7)
      - Hospitals, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 1)
      - Housing, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 2)
      - Inflation, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 3)
      - Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 4)
      - Interior, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 5)
      - Internal Security, 1970 (Box 397, Folder 6)
      - Interstate Commerce, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 7)
      - Merchant Marine, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 8)
      - Metric System, 1969 (Box 397, Folder 9)
      - Military, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 10)
      - Military, Appropriations, 1969 (Box 397, Folder 11)
      - Minimum Wage, 1969 (Box 397, Folder 12)
      - Natural Resources, 1969 (Box 397, Folder 13)
      - Packing, 1970 (Box 397, Folder 14)
      - Panama Canal, 1970 (Box 397, Folder 15)
      - Patent Law, 1970 (Box 397, Folder 16)
      - Pensions, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 17)
      - Petroleum, 1970 (Box 397, Folder 18)
      - Pollution (1 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 19)
      - Pollution (2 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 20)
      - Pollution (3 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box 398, Folder 1)
      - Pollution, Water, Publications, 1969, undated (Box 398, Folder 2)
      - Population, 1970 (Box 398, Folder 3)
      - Postal (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 398, Folder 4)
      - Postal (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 398, Folder 5)
      - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 6)
      - Presidential & Congressional Salaries, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 7)
      - Publications, “Conservation Directory of the National Wildlife Federation”, 1970 (Box 398, Folder 8)
      - Publications, “HEW and Title VI: A Report on the Development of the Organization, Policies, and Compliance Procedures of the Department, of Health, Education, and Welfare Under Title VI of the Civil Rights of 1964.”, 1970 (Box 398, Folder 9)
      - Publications, “The National Debt Ceiling Proposal”, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 10)
      - Publications, “The Pending Unemployment Compensation Amendments”, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 11)
      - Railroad Retirement, 1969-1970 (Box 398, Folder 12)
      - Railroads, 1969-1970 (Box 399, Folder 1)
      - Reclamation, 1969 (Box 399, Folder 2)
      - Recreation, 1970 (Box 399, Folder 3)
      - Re-Districting, 1970 (Box 399, Folder 4)
      - Resolutions by Various Organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 399, Folder 5)
      - Riots and Rioting, 1969 (Box 399, Folder 6)
      - Riots and Rioting, 1970 (Box 399, Folder 7)
      - Sabotage and Vandalism, 1970 (Box 399, Folder 8)
      - Selective Service, 1969-1970 (Box 399, Folder 9)
      - Small Business, 1969-1970 (Box 399, Folder 10)
      - Social Security, 1969 (Box 399, Folder 11)
      - Social Security, 1970 (Box 399, Folder 12)
      - Space, Apollo 11, 1969 (Box 399, Folder 13)
      - Supreme Court, 1969-1970 (Box 399, Folder 14)
      - Tariff, 1970 (Box 400, Folder 1)
      - Taxes, General (1 of 4), 1969 (Box 400, Folder 2)
      - Taxes, General (2 of 4), 1969 (Box 400, Folder 3)
      - Taxes, General (3 of 4), 1969 (Box 400, Folder 4)
      - Taxes, General (4 of 4), 1969 (Box 400, Folder 5)